# JENNIFER HOBBS

Email: jjhobbs204@gmail.com | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/jenhobbs204

Extremely high attention to detail and excellent communication skills. Dedicated, motivated and focused on maintaining a high level of service with clients and colleagues alike. Great deal of experience in the travel industry with a multitude of skills including content load & management, data analytics, hotel procurement and customer service. Previous roles also include working in an agile environment with outsourced development teams and managing the implementation back into the business-as-usual teams.

## **Career History**

### DENMARK - Flight Centre LTD - August 2020 to December 2020

In August 2020 I was called back to work at **Flight Centre LTD** as the **Integrations Manager** for the Global Procurement Network. In this role I used my knowledge from being part of the original development process of our new system to ensure a swift and successful integration. I was expected to test new processes and one best ways, ensure their effectiveness and implement them into the distribution teams. I was also involved in training a range of teams in the new system processes to ensure the entire department was supported for our Go Live date and beyond.

## **DENMARK - Flight Centre LTD – March 2019 to April 2020** (Furlough from April to August 2020)

I worked as part of the Flight Centre LTD Agile Project Team as a Subject Matter Expert (SME) until I was placed on furlough April 2020. Flight Centre has made the decision to move the global company onto a new booking engine platform. The Agile Project team 'Copernicus' has been created to ensure the companies requirements are communicated accurately, the new system is designed to match our needs and with minimal change for our agents on the front end. As an SME for content design, I was expected to provide feedback on user stories, test the new system environments and communicate daily with teams based in Australia, USA, and UK.

### BRITIAN - Flight Centre LTD - November 2017 to March 2019

**Team Leader for Europe Content (GPN)**. I was expected to load and proof hotel and tour contracts into the calypso system for sale to Flight Centre agents globally. A great attention for detail is required as well as an understanding of the systems to ensure rates and inclusion details are loaded correctly. I was expected to maintain important relationships, with both internal selling businesses and external suppliers, analyse contracts and ensure the accuracy and development of my team. I also choose to be involved in the connectivity and systems testing aspect of this role.

During my employment at Flight Centre, I have completed the following in house training modules:

- Leadership Development Program (8 x 3-hour sessions)
- Fierce Conversations (3-hour session)
- Coaching for growth (3-hour session)
- Managing Change (3-hour session)

I have won multiple Customer Service and excellence awards as well as being invited to attend our Global Ball in Singapore 2016 and Berlin 2018. This is our most prestigious award available to only the top 10% of the company globally. During my time leading the team we won the outstanding achievement award and best North content team in January 2019.

## BRITIAN - Flight Centre LTD - October 2015 to November 2017

**Assistant Team Leader for Europe Content (GPN).** As ATL I was expected to assist the Team Leader with implementing business plans and new processes. I was also expected to help develop team members alongside my normal daily responsibilities.

## BRITIAN - Flight Centre LTD - March 2014 to October 2015

**Content Coordinator for the Global Procurement Network (GPN)**. As part of the Europe content team, we were expected to load and proof hotel and service contracts into the calypso system. We were responsible for accurately delivering these products in a speedy manor to all selling partners across the world.

## BRITIAN - Flight Centre LTD - July 2013 to March 2014

**International Travel Consultant** trained to sell all holiday types to potential clients. This is done over e-mail, phone and by walk in. I was expected to tailor make holiday packages, sell these to potential clients, meet daily sales targets as well as use company systems and ensure all payments to suppliers were up to date.

#### BACKPACKING NEW ZEALAND AND AUSTRALIA - June 2011 to June 2013

During this time, I worked in various roles including temp work, ski school childcare, waitressing, bar work, cleaning and hotel reception work.

## BRITIAN - Bumble Bees, Private Day Nursery, Kent - June 2010 to May 2011

I was one of two key people responsible for a group of eight 2-year-olds, using the Early Years Foundation Stages to structure the day, and solely responsible for planning the children's activities. We were also expected to give detailed feedback on each child's development whilst in our care.

# CANADA - Ski Instructor, Blackcomb Mountain, Whistler – November 2008 to April 2009 December 2009 to April 2010 (excl. VANOC)

A Whistler Kids Mini's Ski Instructor involved teaching 3- to 4-year-olds with no ski experience to much higher skiing levels. I was also in charge of their safety and happiness in my care. I was expected to organise daily teaching strategies to encourage the children.

## **Education and Qualifications**

Proficient in using Microsoft office applications (including Excel), project management systems (such as JIRA, Salesforce, Trello) and various travel reservation systems (such as Calypso, Travelbox, Amadeus). I have worked with reporting tools such as Power BI and SQL reporting.

## **Computer languages**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript (including react and react native)
- SQL databases (mongoDB)
- Serverless (AWS)

## 2021 - Full Stack Immersion - CareerFoundry (online)

## 2020 - Intro to Frontend Development - CareerFoundry (online)

2020 - HTML, CSS and Web Design - General Assembly (online)

2019 - Introduction to Agile Project Management – Copenhagen, Denmark

2016 - Basic First Aid in the Workplace - London, UK

2009 - Level One CSIA Ski Instructors Certificate - Vancouver, Canada

2008 - Basic Events Organising Course - University of Exeter, UK

### 2005 to 2008 - 2.1 BA (hons) Degree from University of Exeter, UK - Childhood and Youth Studies.

2003 to 2005 - Hurtwood House School, Guildford, UK - A Levels - Art (A), Chemistry (B) & Biology (C)

1996 to 2003 - British School of Paris, France - GCSE Levels

## **Personal Interests**

### Interests

I am a keen snowboarder and try to go at least once a year. I enjoy socialising with my friends, baking and exploring new cultures across the world. In my spare time I am fascinated by Psychology and spend a lot of time listening to podcasts on society, culture and crime.

## **Volunteer Work**

From January 2017 to March 2018, I volunteered as a Samaritan in the Central London Office. During this time, I went through an intensive ten-week active listening course and learnt to provide emotional support whilst broadening my experience of the world. I was on shift to answer phones once a week as well as being involved in their outreach programmes. These included supporting the Homeless and visiting the local Men's Prison to teach volunteer prisoners on how to become 'listeners' within the prison.